That's what I call,
bro.
Good afternoon.
I've been doing 1 research on anxiety,
stress for college and I wanted to know if you could participate.
It's 2 questions.
Super fast.
Could it be what your name is?
Is Iranian?
With z's or with s's?
Do you think the population's stress anxiety
level has increased or decreased since the pandemic?
It has increased a lot,
a lot,
we have also created a medicine to combat anxiety,
stress, dpm.
Except that it is not on sale,
it is still under evaluation by Anvisa,
it is an anxiolytic to activate dopamine and serotonin.
I wanted to show you,
just for you to give an opinion.
If you find the release of this medicine,
this medicine positive or I can't show you,
it is a medicine of happiness and anti stress,
anti anxiety,
anti PMS.
This
it's really
multi-tank, multi-tank,
multi-tank.